KYLE M. CHAMBERS

Systems IT Analyst

Contact

Location Hoboken, NJ, 07030

<u>Phone</u> 862-579-7933

<u>E-mail</u>

kyle.chambers13@outlook.com

Skills

Python

Tableau

SQL

GIT

HTML/CSS

Microsoft Exchange

SharePoint

PowerShell

Azure

More than 5 years managing, designing, and deploying various tasks for MS Exchange and Web Clients. Migrated and enhanced various Notes/Domino based applications to MS web based applications. Wrote technical manuals, project plans, training manuals and technical/standard-operating procedures. Interested in exciting new collaborative environments.

Work History

2018-01 -Current

Associate Systems Engineer / IT Analyst

Brown Brothers Harriman & Company, Jersey City, NJ Collaboration Engineering & Development - Our team engineers a modern, robust collaborative platform for users and applications on MS Teams, Exchange, SharePoint, Skype for Business

- Migrated 500 IBM Connections applications to SharePoint Environment
- Developed Chatbot to support MS Teams rollout
- Migrated 6,000 users from IBM Domino platform to Microsoft Exchange
- Support and develop Exchange products for client facing parties
- Developed automated reporting solutions for Exchange platform

2016-07 -2018-12

Business Technology Analyst

Brown Brothers Harriman & Company, Jersey City, NJ Two-year rotational program designed to develop business technology professionals out of university.

Education

2012-08 -2016-05

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology & Management

Syracuse University - Syracuse, NY
Minor: Global Enterprise Technology
Phanstiel Scholarship in recognition of academic success
with demonstrated leadership.

Accomplishments



Microsoft 365 Certified Developer Associate

Building Application Solutions with Microsoft 365 Core Services

For developers who design, build, test, and maintain applications and solutions that are optimized for the productivity and collaboration needs of organizations using the Microsoft 365 platform.

Additional Information

My GitHub Page & Profile- https://myfriendkmc.github.io/ My Tableau Profile -

https://public.tableau.com/profile/kyle.chambers#!/